<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Snowplow Hybrid Apps Accelerator</title>
    <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Snowplow Hybrid Apps Accelerator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:24:05 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data upload</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/upload/1-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/upload/1-upload/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of options to load the sample Snowplow data to your Snowflake warehouse. Select the most suitable for your project below.
Attachments upload.zip (118 KB) Python Snowflake Web Interface Download the upload.zip folder which contains the sample_events.csv and the snowflake_upload.py files. You will need both to load the sample data to the Snowflake warehouse with Python.
Step 1: Set up your environment Set up a virtual environment (recommended) and install the snowflake-connector-python package (tested with version 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Snowplow dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/1-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/1-installation/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Add snowplow-mobile package Add the snowplow-web package to your packages.yml file. The latest version can be found here
packages: - package: snowplow/snowplow_mobile version: 0.5.3 Step 2: Install the package Install the package by running:
dbt deps </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing the trackers</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/1-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/1-installation/</guid>
      <description>To instrument tracking, you will need to install tracker libraries both in the Web view as well as the native mobile app.
Snowplow WebView tracker installation To install the WebView tracker in your JavaScript or TypeScript app, add the npm package:
npm install --save @snowplow/webview-tracker You will then be able to use the functions provided by the WebView tracker as follows:
import { trackSelfDescribingEvent } from &amp;#39;@snowplow/webview-tracker&amp;#39;; There is no need to configure the WebView tracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model your pipeline data</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/next_steps/1-run_model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/next_steps/1-run_model/</guid>
      <description>At this stage you should:
Have tracking set-up Have some data in the ATOMIC.EVENTS table Have a working dbt project with the mobile model configurations for the sample data Step 1: Complete refresh of your Snowplow mobile package (Optional) If you would like to use your current dbt environment that you set-up during modelling the sample data you might want to start from scratch.
While you can drop and recompute the incremental tables within this package using the standard --full-refresh flag, all manifest tables are protected from being dropped in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlit</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/visualisation/1-streamlit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/visualisation/1-streamlit/</guid>
      <description>Streamlit uses Python to build shareable dashboards without the need for front-end development experience.
Download the streamlit-visualisation project template and copy the unzipped folder to your project directory to get started.
Attachments streamlit-project-mobile.zip (39 KB) Step 1: Install requirements Run the command below to install the project requirements and run the virtual environment
❗❗ This implementation has been tested with the following dependencies: python=3.9.13, streamlit=1.12.0, snowflake-connector-python==2.7.9. If you run into package compatibility issues or encounter any errors try using them to build your own environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring and using the iOS and Android trackers</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/2-mobile_trackers_usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/2-mobile_trackers_usage/</guid>
      <description>Having installed the tracker dependencies, the next step is to initialize the tracker instances in your app. Tracker instances are initialized given configuration that includes network settings, tracker feature settings, session settings, and more.
The following snippets show how to initialize tracker instances using the default settings. They call the Snowplow.createTracker() function and pass it two required information:
The tracker namespace which uniquely identifies the tracker within the app. Network configuration with the endpoint address of the Snowplow Collector (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set-up and run dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/2-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/2-run/</guid>
      <description>This step assumes you have data in the ATOMIC.SAMPLE_EVENTS table which will be used to demonstrate how to set-up and run the snowplow-mobile dbt package to model Snowplow mobile data.
Step 1: Set-up Variables The snowplow_mobile dbt package comes with a list of variables specified with a default value that you may need to overwrite in your own dbt project&amp;rsquo;s dbt_project.yml file. For details you can have a look at the installed package&amp;rsquo;s default variables which can be found at [dbt_project_name]/dbt_packages/snowplow_mobile/dbt_project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom models</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/next_steps/2-custom_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/next_steps/2-custom_models/</guid>
      <description>If you have got to this stage, congratulations! You are ready to take action and use your Snowplow generated data to help your business grow.
As a next step you might want to check out our detailed guide on how to create custom models to adjust the snowplow-mobile data model to your own needs if the out-of-the box solution does not fully fit your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore Snowplow data</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/3-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/3-test/</guid>
      <description>Data should now be loaded into your warehouse. In this section, we will take a closer look at the output to mitigate data issues and get familiar with the derived tables.
Step 1: Check the output schemas Head to the SQL editor of your choice (e.g.: Snowflake Web UI) to check the model&amp;rsquo;s output. You should be able to see three new schemas created:
[your_custom_schema]_scratch: drop and recompute models that aid the incremental run [your_custom_schema]_derived: main output models you can use in your downstream models and reporting [your_custom_schema]_manifest: tables that help the integrity and core incremental logic of the model Step 2: Explore your data Take some time to familiarise yourself with the derived tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up tracking in Web views</title>
      <link>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/3-webview_usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowplow-incubator.github.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/tracking/3-webview_usage/</guid>
      <description>In the Installation section, you installed the WebView tracker in your JavaScript Web app that is accessed in the mobile Web views. After that, you learned how to configure and use the mobile trackers to track events and subscribe to events from Web views. This section explains how to use the WebView tracker to track events inside Web views.
Event tracking API The tracker provides a set of functions to manually track events.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
