<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modeling on Snowplow Hybrid Apps Accelerator</title>
    <link>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modeling on Snowplow Hybrid Apps Accelerator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Snowplow dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/1-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/1-installation/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Add snowplow-mobile package Add the snowplow-web package to your packages.yml file. The latest version can be found here
packages: - package: snowplow/snowplow_mobile version: 0.5.3 Step 2: Install the package Install the package by running:
dbt deps </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set-up and run dbt Package</title>
      <link>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/2-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/2-run/</guid>
      <description>This step assumes you have data in the ATOMIC.SAMPLE_EVENTS table which will be used to demonstrate how to set-up and run the snowplow-mobile dbt package to model Snowplow mobile data.
Step 1: Set-up Variables The snowplow_mobile dbt package comes with a list of variables specified with a default value that you may need to overwrite in your own dbt project&amp;rsquo;s dbt_project.yml file. For details you can have a look at the installed package&amp;rsquo;s default variables which can be found at [dbt_project_name]/dbt_packages/snowplow_mobile/dbt_project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore Snowplow data</title>
      <link>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/3-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.snowplow.io/snowplow-hybrid-apps-accelerator/en/modeling/3-test/</guid>
      <description>Data should now be loaded into your warehouse. In this section, we will take a closer look at the output to mitigate data issues and get familiar with the derived tables.
Step 1: Check the output schemas Head to the SQL editor of your choice (e.g.: Snowflake Web UI) to check the model&amp;rsquo;s output. You should be able to see three new schemas created:
[your_custom_schema]_scratch: drop and recompute models that aid the incremental run [your_custom_schema]_derived: main output models you can use in your downstream models and reporting [your_custom_schema]_manifest: tables that help the integrity and core incremental logic of the model Step 2: Explore your data Take some time to familiarise yourself with the derived tables.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
